Workplace visits, a miserable event where we get split into groups, sent to some company and have to write up a report on it all.
The workplaces I really want to visit are crime scenes, medical coroners, our drug cartels.
The sort of work that shows the darkest corners of our society.
Get in groups of six with those that have similar interests.
Okay!
Unfortunately, there's an even bigger problem at hand here.
Okay, I want to go to Nagasaki Hut.
Yeah, great, but we're drawing straws.
compromising the red ray of blue,
The Herz's hand's watermelon
As long as I can't see
You would're sad when you feel,
like
Honest Sonu
Are you kidding? Groups of six with similar interests? Seriously?
Ichikawa, you can join us.
Oh, okay. Yeah, thanks.
So be it. I'll help them fill their group.
Won't be hard to stay out of sight in a group like theirs.
Yo, look! Yamada only has a group of four, so they need two more!
But...Hara's group only has four also, so they need another two.
If that's the case, wanna split up then?
Not like we have a choice.
What? Hey, wait.
Hey, mind adding me and Ota?
Huh?
Hang on a sec. If we're taking anyone, it would definitely be those two guys over the two of you.
S-Sekimi!
Right?
I don't care who, but just not Adachi.
Wait, what?
What's your problem? Did you imagine you'd join us yourself or something?
Uh, no. That's not it. It's just Kanzuki here who is thinking of joining Hara.
Shhh! Shhh!
That's not really a secret to me or Yamada anymore.
Hmm.
Huh.
Okay then. How about us girls have our own little draft pick to choose from the four of you boys?
What? Why should you be the one to decide for us all, huh?
Way to be a bitch.
Oh. Is that the way you ought to be speaking to me?
Ooh.
Zoe.
How bad does he want to be in this group?
Just hang on a minute, alright?
Let's do majority rules. Who wants Adachi?
That's Big Zero.
What? Big Zero?
Ugh, there's no way I'm getting picked.
Okay, next is Ota.
Wait a sec. Shouldn't we talk this out as a group before we vote?
Who is it that you want then?
It's not that I want someone in particular.
Pretty normal I'd say.
Yeah?
How normal is your normal though?
I see.
Okay, let's go with that then.
Ugh, fine by me.
Right. We've made our decision.
First pick of the draft to join us is...
Tanzuki!
Selected by three out of the four of us.
Ugh.
Why is this super perv so popular?
Oh, but I...
Oh God! Wait just a minute. Hang on a sec.
Hmm? Why? You object to him?
No, that's not it. I just thought we should ask him first or something, you know? Right?
Uh, oh. I mean, I just...
This is pointless. There's no way he can turn them down like this.
Uh, this just means the offer's there. Not that you actually have to join.
You study hard and have good grades, right?
Huh? I mean, they're not bad.
You'd probably be better off in that group over there then.
Ichikawa?
This isn't some game. This is meant as a learning event.
I mean, he'd be better off with smarter...
Whoops.
Good point, Ichikawa.
Guess this group is my only hope since I'm a dummy.
Yeah, me too.
Wait, what?
Um, I got a 40 in science.
Uh-huh.
And that matters to us how?
Damn, he's stupider than me.
A real earnest idiot.
All right, then I guess me and Ichikawa will join you and round out our team of dummies.
Huh?
Who said we're dumb?
Watch your damn mouth.
I'm fifth in our ear!
Great!
We'll just go join the other team then.
Right.
Okay, class.
All grouped up yet?
Jeez.
Feels like that did more harm than good.
That was a lie.
How?
How in the world did she know?
I wonder, did Yamada realize I wanted to be in the same group as her?
She couldn't have.
And besides, I wasn't trying to join them anyway.
I was being altruistic.
All I wanted to do was to help Kanzaki join Hara's group.
What is going on with those two?
Oh, hi there, Hara.
Quit being so obvious!
Oh!
Triple potato flavor!
That worked?
Actually, I can't.
I'm still on a really strict diet right now.
Why'd you come over here then?
Oh, well, I kinda want to talk to you about something.
Really?
You do?
Hurray!
You picked me over snacks!
Second's in, and we're already verging on Moe manga territory.
But Hara, if I recall, didn't Kanzaki say he liked curvy girls a lot?
You can't fall for what he said!
It's a lie!
That rule only applies for girls who are already pretty to begin with!
I got to lose some weight if I want any hope!
How come?
You're a real super cutie!
I'm not a cutie!
Hey, Hara, how are things going with him?
Well, actually, we...
Trying to help her keep it secret, huh?
The two of you went out together!
And now it's all for nothing!
Keep your voice down!
Sorry!
We only went out shopping!
That perv's making progress!
How far did you go?
What?
Do you mean, like, did we...
To Shibuya?
Huh?
Oh, just Kuyama.
What did you think she meant?
Oh, yeah?
Cool!
That's so great!
I've always wanted to talk about this kind of stuff!
She doesn't care for this sort of girl talk!
Oh, yeah, cool!
That's so great!
I've always wanted to talk about this kind of stuff!
She doesn't care for this sort of girl talk!
Oh, really?
I'd love to hear all about your stories too, Yamada!
I bet you have lots more to talk about than I do!
This is definitely bordering on stuff I shouldn't be here for!
Like boyfriends?
I'm single!
You've had a boyfriend before though, right?
I haven't!
I'm sorry!
I just assumed, since you're so popular in school,
that you would be dating a little girl!
You're so popular in school,
you would be dating a little girl!
I don't know!
It's cool that you would be dating someone super charming or something like that!
I don't need one to be able to offer advice though, okay?
Quit being so obviously being!
You ever imagine what it's like?
Cause I think about it all the time!
She's really going deep, huh?
Is there anything special you want to do once you have a boyfriend?
Wha-what do you mean by want to do?
Harachou!
I would do this!
Huh?
Share a pair of earbuds together!
Oh!
You meant that!
We should take a selfie!
Ah!
Say Cheetos!
Sorry!
I was trying to make my face smaller!
Girls are always doing that!
Then there's this!
Ah!
Holding hands inside my pocket!
Oh!
Good idea!
Ah!
What a slob!
Let's use your pocket!
Ah!
Bye Choco!
I...
I was planning on giving that to you, you know?
Here...
You should have it!
Ah!
Maybe just this once!
Oh!
Mmm!
It's so good!
Glad to hear it!
If only this could last forever!
What is it?
A ghost?
No...
But I think...
I know who...
Huh?
Hey!
Oh!
It was you!
I guess it's fine if he heard all that then!
Doubt anyone would hear it from him!
Hmm?
Was that a dig at me?
Are the two of you always in here together?
Whenever I don't have any work, yeah!
Wow!
Really?
What?
No way!
I've always come here every day since the very beginning!
Yamada just started showing up one day out of the blue!
Now, we just, you know...
Hmm...
Huh?
Let me know if you make any progress!
Same to you!
She doesn't have a boyfriend...
Never has, either...
But...
So what?
It's got nothing to do with me...
Maybe...
Something really is wrong with me...
Huh?
It's raining?
A storm rolls in out of nowhere...
People share umbrellas...
Bump shoulders...
A bonding moment for social types...
But not for me...
Huh?
Oh, that's right!
I forget!
You ride your bike!
Huh?
What's that got to do with anything?
Wait...
Would she have asked to share an umbrella if I had one?
Hmm...
That looks big!
Hey, I know!
Let me wear it!
Huh?
But I...
Let me borrow it!
So I can go buy an umbrella from the convenience store!
Why?
I can just go do that!
That'd be a bit much to ask!
Hurry and take it off!
Huh?
It's perfect!
gin!
That's perfect!
wearing my raincoat I'll be right back alrighty I will come back I promise you
I wasn't afraid you wouldn't if this were anime that'd be my last line just go
already hearing her say that does make me kind of worried though is that her
bag it's her wallet in here but I mean even if it is she has her charge card
right of course
but hey hey yeah your bag your wallet what oh I I was just trying to keep it dry
this is so you don't get wet top pouch my wallet is in there can you get it out
and put it in my pocket huh
what we have that it's broken
this yeah don't put it in that pocket I'm gonna get too wet put it in my shirt pocket
huh
good thank you now you should run on back Ichikoa you hurry too
did she just not want to admit her mistake or maybe she was just hoping to share an umbrella
I'm back
okay maybe she just wanted to go buy snacks
Ichikoa do you like mint chocolate don't care either way what now but almost everyone either
loves it or hates it no one's ever neutral on it oh really she bought pie choco guess she really
wanted it after all hmm so tell me do I love it or do I hate it the answer is out of the wrapper
already
your time is up that was fast yeah it was a test of your reaction time
should have said so first later
for you it's yours
ice cream
want something else
yep no doubt about it there's definitely something wrong with me
I like her
thank you Yamada
ichikawa
I never told you the final answer
huh
I'm in love
with mint chocolate right
only with mint chocolate
I'd never shouted that loud in my entire life
it's finally time for our workplace visit
oh I want fair cheeky
well too bad
I might have wound up in Yamada's group but that doesn't mean I can suddenly talk with these
girls
some milk tea then
no drinks either idiot
seriously
hey I think this is it
oh
which one of them at the front desk is your type
shut up
that means the only person I have to talk with is this guy
thank you very much
sure
someone's coming down to guide us
well despite what you think I actually know a lot about manga
stuff like 1p hunter and attack on
I've got a bad feeling about this
and this is the editor's office
sorry not yet
please come on in
wow
that's adorable
do you know this one
not at all
how about that
no idea
she doesn't know what damn one
hey Yamada
you read much manga
uh
afraid not
yeah
yeah readings for losers
I get wanting to give the same answer and all
but at this rate
yeah
uh
you're gonna have nothing to talk about man
oh
that's Yuri Araki
we're in the same agency
you are
with Yuri
yeah
do you know her
isn't she cute
oh no
why'd this have to be where they have something in common
yeah
I love her
or those boobs at least
those g-cup knockers are what I really want to get my hands on
um
I mean that
glad he's such a moron
wow
something you like
yeah there is
I love Crows and Worst
I can't believe you really have it
oh
is Crows published here
you actually know Crows and Worst
it's a how-to guide for guys
even I know the manga
it's the one with all the hot ass guys in it right
yeah
shut up
wanna see the original art
wow
can we really
talk about a major rift in the group
normally speaking
I'd be on their side
but
it would be so lame
to get worked up
over some dumb manga
okay kiddos
take a look here
these Baki originals
whoa
Baki
I
I wanna see those
aren't you gonna look
huh
um
be cool
sure
maybe I'd like a little peek
hey now
you're blocking Ichikawa's view
what
no wait
come on now
step aside
it's a real Baki draft
I never realized how detailed these were
they use so many screen tone layers
wow
this is cool
yeah
huh
you gotta give me more than that
so
do you all have any other questions
I do
in stuff with lots of pervy fan service with huge knockers
do artists usually draw while looking at the real
no
they do not
oh
can you please shut up
that sort of stuff is all made up fantasy
I know that
sometimes the point is just to ask the question
make some room coming in
what do I do
no matter where I look
it's bad
only one choice left
with my eyes closed
my other senses are heightened
she smells nice
I can hear her breathing
and then there's her
we made it
huh
what is it
this must be what it's like in a pervy fan
it's the way they draw those muscles
you know what I mean
so Ichikawa
do you read a lot of manga
well
more than some
if we're just talking Akita publishing
there's Baki and Beastars
and also Mitsudomoe
dang it
chill out me
what else
uh
well Togen Anki is kind of popular right now
yeah
she has a thing for just staring at people doesn't she
that sounds totally cool
the only manga I really know is Kimi Iro Octave
oh
that's the girls manga they made into a movie right
that one's not from Akita
where's it from then
Shugaku-kan I believe
oh yeah right Gaku-kan
Gaku-kan
have you ever read that manga
I have not
would you like to borrow it
huh
as if
like Ichikawa would want to read some sweet lovey-dovey girly manga
funny
were they both just making fun of me
excuse me for a second
okay we're taking the train that leaves at 20 past
damn it
damn it all
like this gloomy little creepy freak would even read anything as light-hearted as that
hahahaha
I knew it
doesn't matter that I realized I like her
because she'd never
hey where did everybody go
you didn't tell them where I was
I thought they heard you
ah
wow
huh
ゆうゆうに
朝の宇宙
近づきそうな距離でも
わからなくなる夕暮れ
迷い込んでいる迷路の
出口はどこか
異常が日常になって
反則黙って待って
別にどうでもいい 素直になれない
いつまでもこのままでいたいかも
そんな気持ちは解けた
僕らは探してた お揃いの心を
僕らは交わしてた まとまらないセリフを
触れたい手の熱が 心まで届いて
僕は背伸びしてた 大人見てる
君は見てしたいんだ 君のこと
時間が消えたって 夢じゃなくて
心が痛くてもっと
言葉にしたくて